instantcashsweepstakes.com 2014-10-10

# Instant Cash Sweepstakes Terms

### The Privacy Policy of InstantCashSweepstakes.com and PaidViewPoint.com 

**Policy Effective Date:** November 2008  
**Last Revised:** March 23, 2011  
This page discloses the privacy policy and practices of the InstantCashSweepstakes.com (ICS) and PaidViewPoint.com website (PV), sites owned and operated by Umongous, Inc. (collectively referred to as **Umongous** hereafter), a New Jersey Inc. 

Umongous in is the market research and opinion research business. Umongous operates ICS and PV for the purpose of gaining anonymous opinions, such as your opinions, in order to help its clients gain a better understanding of their business and strategic opportunities. The clients of Umongous use this information in an aggregate fashion and are not interested in your identity or the individual identities of other ICS or PV panel members. It is against Umongous policy and market research terms of service (MR-TOS) for one of its clients to seek to determine the individual identity of an ICS or PV panel member. 

#### Our Privacy Pledge:

##### When you participate at ICS as a member, your privacy is assured.

You will notice when you register at ICS or PV that we do not ask for your full name. We ask for a user name for the purpose of addressing you in emails and displaying your wins to our community on our home page and past winners pages. You are free to supply a pseudonym as your first name and initial on ICS and a pseudonym on PV. We are not interested in your real name. We also do not ask for your precise address. We ask for your state, county and zip code. We ask for your email address at registration. We will not rent, sell or share your email address with anyone without your expressed permission, except in the rare instances required by law. 

You are able, at your option, to upload an avatar into your account. This is entirely voluntary. The avatar may be your true likeness or photo at your sole discretion. If you choose to upload an avatar, ICS and PV may from time to time display your avatar on publicly viewable portions of the website and label the avatar with your first name, first initial of last name supplied at registration and account winnings or cash out. Your avatar may be overlaid on a [map](http://www.instantcashsweepstakes.com/map) of the United States and show your approximate registered location such as a region in your state. The map has names of states but does not have cities labeled. Umongous will not share your avatar with Umongous clients or associate it with any survey answers. Should you decline to upload an avatar, ICS and PV may on occasion display a stock avatar image along with your first name, first initial of last name and account winnings or cash out. 

We do share your anonymous demographics, which you supply during registration or periodically update, with our clients, along with your survey answers. Although our clients are not interested in your personal identity, and we do not record your full name, address or phone number, theoretically (in unusual circumstances), there could be cases where our clients might be able to determine your personal identity. An example would be if you live in a zip code with a very small population and your demographics are unique for that zip code. In practice, we are unaware of any of our clients making this effort. Such an effort by Umongous clients is against our policy and MR-TOS. Because our Umongous survey system is self-service, it is possible that one of our clients could potentially violate our policies and MR-TOS and deploy a survey into ICS that requests personally identifiable information (PIA). We urge you not to answer any question in a market research survey that requests PIA such as your real name, address, phone number, social security number or email address. If you see such a question in a survey on ICS, please report this violation to us at privacy [at] instantcashsweepstakes [dot] com. If you see such a violation on PV, please report this violation to notification [at] paidviewpoint [dot] com. 

Umongous will never try to sell you anything. We will never share, rent, sell or provide your email address to anyone else who might want to sell you anything. We are not in the lead generation business and it is against our MR-TOS for Umongous clients to use our system and attempt to access you through ICS or PV for that purpose. 

Your individual responses to surveys will also be kept confidential and will never be linked to your personal identifying information WITH THE EXCEPTION THAT Umongous does supply the demographics supplied by you at registration and kept updated by you in your profile including state, county, zip code and inferred city or town. This information is supplied to Umongous clients along with your survey answers so that they can make determinations about the opinions of people who generically are similar to you. 

If you ever see a survey that you do not wish to answer, exit the current session in your browser and come back to ICS or PV at a later time. It will be removed from your account due to completion of the number of responses ordered by the Umongous client, and no longer appear when you log in to ICS or PV. Do not answer any survey which you do not wish to participate in. 

Many of the surveys you will encounter while participating at ICS and PV exist for the purpose of identifying certain psychographic characteristics such as interests, activities, personal opinions and possessions. Umongous uses this information to direct certain surveys by Umongous clients to you. For example, you might be asked if you own a pickup truck because a Umongous client either does or doesn't wish to survey people who own pickup trucks. 

Many questions asked in non-market-research surveys shown to you at ICS and PV are used by Umongous to make a determination about whether you are carefully reading questions and providing deliberate, consistent and candid answers. Your answers to these questions are used to determine whether Umongous will ask you to complete market research surveys. The magnitude of your opportunity to win prizes at ICS and monetary compensation on PV is largely predicated upon your level of activity at ICS and PV AND our determination of whether you are reading questions carefully and providing deliberate, consistent, candid answers. We use our proprietary algorithm "TrustScore" to make that determination. Umongous is always seeking to provide the highest quality service to its clients and looks to you to be candid and truthful with your opinions. 

##### Other information Collected by ICS and PV During Your Visits

ICS automatically collects information and records in its database log files to help administer the site and aid in technical problem solving. Examples of log file information collected include IP address, time a page was viewed, your browser type, URL parameters, and information from cookies that were set by ICS and PV at the time of the visit. IP addresses are correlated with your declared location such as zip code. Use of proxy servers to mask your location is a violation of ICS and PV TOS (terms of service). It is important for ICS to prevent users from creating and operating multiple accounts. Log file information is never linked to personal identifying information other than the information provided in your account profile. 

##### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Umongous. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

##### There are Times When We Learn Your Name or Other PIA

We may learn your name on certain occasions, but we do not store it within the ICS and PV databases or use it for any other purpose than to resolve a customer support issue initiated by you. For instance, if you send us an email, your name may be revealed to us in your email address, or because you have used your name in your email. If you post a message on our [blog](https://www.facebook.com/InstantCashSweepstakes) or [Get Satisfaction](http://getsatisfaction.com/instantcashsweepstakescom) page, you may choose to sign it with your real name. We do not encourage you to publically reveal your name even though no 3rd parties will be able to see your registration demographics or other personal information. When we send you money by PayPal.com, your name may be revealed to us in our Paypal account but we will not transfer your name to the ICS or PV database. We have no interest in knowing your personal identity. 

##### Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews/User Feedback

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web sites, which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent to post their name along with their testimonial via email prior to posting the testimonial. 

##### Inviting Friends to Join ICS

When you invite a friend to join ICS using the tools provided to you by ICS, a code will be shared with them in order to link them to you in our database, so that you can receive matched wins as stated in our rules. The first name and first initial of their last name that they use in their registration will be shown to you in your profile section entitled: "My Friends (already invited)". There you will be able to see their first name, initial and details of matched wins events. When you answer fun surveys (non-market research surveys), you will be able to see the answer choices of your invited friends shown anonymized in aggregate. If you have only one invited friend, they will not effectively be anonymized. The same is true for you if you are the only invited friend of another ICS member. If you are uncomfortable with supplying an answer for a fun survey because of this, select the skip button and don't answer that survey. 

ICS also utilizes a third party service, Janrain Engage to facilitate inviting friends and logging into ICS using your other social website login credentials such as your Facebook login. Please refer to the Janrain Privacy policy for further details. ICS does not receive, see or store your third party website login credentials when you use the Janrain widget on ICS. If you invite friends through the widget we do not see their information or email addresses unless they register with ICS as a result of your invitation. Janrain Engage allows ICS to publish information to your social news feeds and profile pages at these websites based upon your permission and the rules of those sites. You can choose to bypass Janrain Engage simply by logging into ICS using your ICS login credentials. 

##### Inviting Friends to Join PV

When you invite a friend to subscribe or become a member of the Website using the tools provided to you by Company, a code will be provided to them to become linked to you in our Website database ("Linked"). Once linked, to the friend that you referred (the "Referral"), you will become eligible to potentially receive a recruiting bonus. The user name and email address (supplied by you) of your invited friend may be shown to you in your profile. Company also utilizes a third party service, Janrain Engage to help facilitate Users' ability to invite Referrals and log into the Website using other social network website login credentials. Please refer to the Janrain Privacy policy for further details. The Company will not receive, see or store your third party social network login credentials when you use the Janrain Engage widget on the Website. If you invite friends through the Janrain Engage widget we will not see their information or email addresses unless they register as a member of the Website as a result of your invitation. By using Janrain Engage, you may agree to allow us to publish information to your social network news feeds and profile pages. You can choose to bypass Janrain Engage by logging into the Website using your regular/default login credentials. 

##### Data Security

ICS has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. These procedures are in place to secure ICS member email addresses, anonymous demographics, psychographics and survey answers. ICS members may access their demographics within their profile page for the purposes of verifying and updating. Under no circumstance can one member view the demographics of another member. As with any Internet endeavor, absolute security of information transmitted through channels (communication networks, hardware, software) not directly operated or controlled by us cannot be guaranteed. 

In the event ICS, PV and/or Umongous or its affiliates enters into a merger, acquisition, sale or other transaction pursuant to which ICS and/or PV, or any portion of Umongous assets is acquired by a third party or an affiliate of Umongous, your personal information may be disclosed to the third party or affiliate both before and after the transaction, for the sole purpose of facilitating the transfer of your account and effecting that transaction. In the event a transaction is consummated, you will be notified of the transaction via email and/or through a notice on our website, and custody of your personal information will be transferred subject to all the terms and restrictions in this privacy policy. In the event the transaction is not consummated, ICS, PV and Umongous will require the third party or affiliate not to use or disclose your personal information in any manner whatsoever and to completely erase the same. 

As is the case with any information you provide to any business operating in the United States, information provided to ICS and/or PV is subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders. 

##### Policies on Correcting and Updating Personal Information

ICS and PV rely on its members themselves to provide any updates to demographic information. 

To change your personal information on ICS, please click on the My Profile link on the top right hand corner and then scroll down to "Account information". If you wish to change or delete your email address, contact us at support [at] instantcashsweepstakes [dot] com and we will be happy to assist you within 2 business days. 

To change your personal information on PV, please log into your PV account and click on the profile link on the top right hand corner of the page. Then choose "settings" from the menu provided. If you wish to change your demographic information, please click on the profile link at the top right-hand corner of the webpage and choose the "my demographics" link. If you wish to contact us for assistance, please email us at support [at] paidviewpoint [dot] com. 

#### Opt Out Policy:

##### You Can Decide at Any Time to End Participation

You can decline to respond to any survey by either selecting the "skip" button for non-market-research surveys or logging out of a session when faced with a market research survey and then logging back in at a later time when it is no longer being shown to you. You may cancel your membership on ICS at anytime by writing ICS at cancellations [at] instantcashsweepstakes [dot] com. IF you desire to cancel your membership in PV, please contact us at notifications [at] paidviewpoint [dot] com. We will promptly cancel your account, delete your information from our database and send you a confirmation email. We respect your decision to decline participation and will not make any attempt to dissuade you. 

#### Use of Cookies and tracking technology:

##### How We Use Cookies & Other Technologies on Our Website

ICS and PV use cookies during your sessions. Cookies are used for technical purposes to allow for accurate transmission of survey information to the ICS database and to ensure that a member does not take the same survey more than once. ICS and PV also use cookies to help ensure that members abide by the rules of one account allowed per member. 

ICS and PV use cookies to store user login credentials automatically, if voluntarily elected by the user, to eliminate the necessity of having to repeatedly retype this information. For users' convenience, this cookie is stored for subsequent sessions. The ICS web server also creates cookies to uniquely identify each user session when a member visits the site. 

Because cookies are used to identify legitimate members and protect unauthorized access to their specific member information, users who choose not to allow cookies cannot register nor can they access the full features of ICS and PV such as opportunities to participate in market research survey or earn cash prizes. 

##### Third Party Cookies

Our privacy statement does not cover the use of cookies by our analytics providers and service providers. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site and use our checkout process for payments. Our analytics providers use tracking cookies to provide us with information on your navigation of our site for support purposes and marketing communications. 

##### Web Beacons

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns. 

##### ICS and PV May Use Digital Fingerprinting

Digital fingerprinting is a technology used to place a unique identifier on a device such as a computer or smartphone. ICS and PV digital fingerprinting will never change the functionality of a device, collect personal information, or affect the operating system or its settings in any way. It will never log keystrokes or record activities. It will never interfere with or take control of the device. It will never send any information to the ICS servers other than the device ID. It will never act as malware, adware, a virus or a Trojan. Its sole purpose is to match the device ID to the ICS or PV accounts logged into from the device. It is used to ensure the integrity of the market research results obtained at ICS and PV. It is also used to help prevent violations of the one account per ICS or PV member rule. ICS and PV use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that this technology is safe, secure and does not cause undue privacy or data security risks. ICS and PV will use and distribute this technology in an ethical manner in accordance with the ICS privacy policy and all applicable laws. 

#### Children's Privacy

The site is intended for adults in the United States. We do not intentionally or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 and we request that individuals under the age of 13 not submit any personal information on the site. If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has created an account at ICS or PV, we will promptly close that account and delete any submitted information. 

#### How and When ICS and PV May Contact You

##### Uses of Information

On PV only - During the registration process we will require your telephone number to identify your account as unique and prohibiting users from creating multiple accounts. Your telephone number is used during the registration process once to verify the account. When you register for your account we will send a confirmation code to your phone. This code is entered into your account to confirm validity of your phone number. 

The only other use of this phone number is to verify a payout request made from your active account. When you log onto your account and request a payout to PayPal, a confirmation code is sent to your phone. This confirmation code must be entered into your account to effectuate the payout. We do use a third party application to dial and send the confirmation code to your phone. At no other time or function on PV is your phone number used or shared. 

##### Invitations

ICS or PV may send you an email from time to time to invite you to take a survey. You may opt-out from receiving ICS or PV emails by selecting the opt-out link in the email. 

##### Reminder Emails

ICS or PV may send you an email to remind you that you can return to the site to begin answering surveys. These reminder emails are sent at your specific request based upon a setting that you have made in your account. If you do not request another reminder be sent to you next time, then none will be sent. To change these settings on PV, please log into your account and click on the profile link in the top right-hand corner, then click on the settings tab where you can turn off these notifications. To change these settings in ICS, please email us at support [at] instantcashsweepstakes [dot] com. [To no longer receive reminder emails from ICS, simply do not check this option once you have completed your session] 

##### Service-related Announcements

From time-to-time we may send you service-related transactional emails. You may opt-out from receiving these emails by selecting the opt-out link in the email. 

##### Promotional Emails

Occasionally we may send you a promotional email concerning some feature, service or promotion directly related to ICS or one of Umongous' related websites. You may opt-out from receiving these emails by selecting the opt-out link in the email. We will never send you a promotional email related to a product or service that is not part of the Umongous business and related websites. 

#### How We Notify You About Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

**Data Retention:** We will retain your information for as long as your account is active, or as needed, to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, please contact us. ICS members contact support [at] instantcashsweepstakes [dot] com and PV members contact support [at] paidviewpoint [dot] com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

#### How to Contact Us About Your Privacy Concerns

ICS can be reached at any time by email at privacy [at] instantcashsweepstakes [dot] com. PV can be reached at any time by email at privacy [at] paidviewpoint [dot] com. It is our practice to respond to emails in less than 48 hours. If we do not respond within 48 hours, call us at 415-364-8601 and leave a message including your email address so we can respond via email. We will respond to your voicemail within one business day. You can also write us at: Umongous, Inc. 123 10th St. San Francisco, CA 94103
